softwaredriverdownload.com 2017-05-13

# Privacy Statement – Software Driver Download

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT CAREFULLY. Privacy is very important to us. We also understand that privacy is very important to you. This Privacy Statement tells you how we protect and use information that we gather through this web site.

## Introduction

The information we receive, and how we use it, depends on what you do when visiting our web site. We collect and use your non-personal information (information that is not identifiable to you personally) differently than your personal information.

## Advertising Choices

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information (e.g., the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. 

These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Non-personal information

Non-personal information is information we collect through this web site that does not identify you as an individual person. It may include information such as the following:

  1. the type of web browser software you use (for example, Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) 
  2. the name of the domain from which you access the Internet 
  3. the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our web site 
  4. the date and time you access our web site 
  5. which pages you have visited on our web site 

Usually these information is used to analyze visitor trend and help us to improve our website. This information is collected from your computer’s web browser: If you only read or download information on our web site, we do not collect or learn your name, e-mail address, home address, or other personal information about you.

* New Changes on 27 Feb 2008: Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on website users visitors’ browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on this website. Please see following information about user options for cookie management.

==========================================================================================  
* New Changes on 20 Mac 2009: Addition of following information about Google and the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx):

  1. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. 
  2. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. 
  3. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

* Data collection of non-personally identifying information:  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).  
==========================================================================================

### To disable cookies on IE

  1. First click on TOOLS at the top of the screen, then click on INTERNET OPTIONS. 
  2. Click on the Privacy Tab. 
  3. Next click on the ADVANCED button. 
  4. You will see the Advanced Privacy Settings dialogue box. Select the Override automatic cookie handling option. 
  5. First Party cookies are cookies set by the website you are visiting and Third Party cookies refer to cookies that are set by a different site to the one you are visiting. 
  6. Three choices for each type of cookie: 
    * Accept – Accepts any cookies. 
    * Block – Blocks all cookies. 
    * Prompt – Asks you before storing a cookie. 
  7. Your choice for the 3 options will depend on your requirements, select whichever settings you want and then click the OK button. For best security measurement, select Block for both First-party and Third-party cookies. 

### Disable cookies in Firefox 2.0

  1. Open the Tools menu. 
  2. Select Options. 
  3. Select the Privacy tab. 
  4. Remove the check mark from “Accept cookies” field. 
  5. Click OK. 

### Disable cookies in Firefox 1.x

  1. Open the Tools menu. 
  2. Select Options. 
  3. Select the Privacy tab. 
  4. Click the View cookies in the “Cookies” area and remove the check mark from the box next to “Allow sites to set cookies”. 
  5. Click OK. 

### Disable cookies in Mozilla

  1. Open the Edit menu and choose Preferences. 
  2. Under the Privacy & Security category, choose Cookies. (If no subcategories are visible, double-click the category to expand the list.) 
  3. Put the radio buttons for “Block cookies”. 
  4. Click “OK”. 

### Disable cookies in Opera 9.0

  1. Open the Tools menu. 
  2. Select Preferences 
  3. OPen the “Advanced” tab 
  4. Select “Cookies” item. 
  5. Put the radio button for “Never accept cookies” option. 
  6. Click OK. 

### Disable cookies in Opera 8.x

  1. Open the Tools menu. 
  2. Select Preferences to open Dialog box. 
  3. Open the Advanced tab. 
  4. Select “Cookies”. 
  5. Select “Refuse all cookies” in Normal cookies combo box and/or Third-party cookies combo box depending on your needs. 
  6. Click OK. 

### Disable cookies Netscape 8.x

  1. Select Tools -> Options. 
  2. Select “Site Controls”. 
  3. Open the “Site List” tab. 
  4. In the “Web features” area, remove the check mark next to “Allow cookies” option. 
  5. Click “OK”. 

### Disable cookies Netscape 7.x

  1. Open the Edit menu. 
  2. Select Preferences to open Dialog box. 
  3. Select the Privacy & Security to open sub-menu. 
  4. Select the Cookies item. 
  5. Select “Disable cookies”. 
  6. Click “OK”. 

The above list pretty much covers major web browsers in the mean time. If your web browser is not in the list above and you wish to know how to disable cookies, please refer to your web browsers’ user manual for steps to do that. Alternatively you can let me know your browser type by using the contact info listed on this page. I will try to include in the list. Sorry for any inconveniences caused.

## Contact

If you have questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please see the [Contact](http://www.softwaredriverdownload.com/contact) form on contact information.
